zikbay.com 2011-11-06

# Zikbay Privacy Policy

####  This privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information. We collect, use, and share personal information to help the zikbay website (“zikbay”) work and to keep it safe (details below). 

###  Collection 

Information posted on zikbay is obviously publicly available. Our computers are currently located in the United States. Zikbay holds and transmits your information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. Therefore, if you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information on our computers in United States. We collect and store the following personal information: · email address, computer sign-on data, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information; · other information, including users IP address and standard web log information. 

###  Use 

We use users’ personal information to: · provide our services; · resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems; · encourage safe trading and enforce our policies; · customize users’ experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates; · communicate marketing and promotional offers to you; · do other things for users as described when we collect the information. 

###  Disclosure 

We don’t sell or rent users’ personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with: · corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services. · service providers who help with our business operations. 

###  Using Information from zikbay 

You may use personal information gathered from zikbay only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn’t agreed to that. 

###  Marketing 

If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you can simply email us at any time. 

###  Security 

We use many tools to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, but as you probably know, nothing’s perfect, so we make no guarantees. 

General 

We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next post or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, and this other company shall be entitled to share your personal information with other companies but at all times otherwise respecting your personal information in accordance with this policy.
